<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Matteo Bobba</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Matteo Bobba</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/research/</guid>
      <description>My research revolves around issues on the accumulation of human capital and the functioning of labor markets in low and middle income countries.&#xA;Working Papers Enhancing Human Capital in Children. A Case Study on Scaling (with Francesco Agostinelli and Ciro Avitabile). Revise and Resubmit (fourth round), Journal of Political Economy. VoxDev Column.&#xA;Teacher Compensation and Structural Inequality: Evidence from Centralized Teacher School Choice in Peru (with Tim Ederer, Gianmarco Léon-Ciliotta, Chris Neilson, and Marco Nieddu).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a Professor of Economics at the Toulouse School of Economics (TSE) in France. My academic research focuses on topics in Development, Labor, and Public Economics. I am also interested in methodological aspects of Policy Evaluation, and in particular in combining model-based and design-based approaches.&#xA;Prior to my academic career, I have been an Economist at the Inter-American Development Bank in Washington DC.&#xA;I am a Research Fellow at the CEPR (Development and Labor), IZA, and EUDN.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
